think that gold from here will likely in
the short term experience weakness going
into like midepptember, maybe even
midocctober at the latest. It'll likely
be caused by the dollar going up.
But I think that gold will likely print
a higher low like midepptember to mid
October, like a higher low and then from
there go back up. if it prints a lower
low, I still wouldn't give up on the
idea, right? Like, yes, it's possible
that you have a slightly lower low. Um,
but I I wouldn't wouldn't make that sort
of like the baseline expectation. I
suppose the lower low would be like if
it were to be back testing this trend
line or something, right? Maybe in that
case you you come back down and you
sweep the low from June and and in that
case you would actually be following
2018 in 2022 where the low occurs in
September, October.